

# Profile

I am a B.E CSE Undergraduate, My passion towards this tech field has continuously driven me to expand my knowledge, experience and skills. Throughout my life, I've approached every challenge with enthusiasm, creativity, and ceaseless desire to expand my knowledge. This have paved the way to countless opportunities and unique experiences.

#### **Skills**

Java	• • • •
Python	• • • •
С	• • • •
Data Structures	• • • •
Problem Solving	• • • •
HTML5	• • • •
CSS3	• • • •
Java Script	• • • • •
Bootstrap	• • • •
Communication	• • • •
Leadership	• • • •

# SHANMUGA PRIYA M

shanmugapriyashanu2002@gmail.com



+91 9080888421





7,RajNagar 3rd Street, Shanthi Nagar, Madurai-625018











✓ Gmail

# **Professional Experience**

Summer Intern (Internship)

ZOHO, Chennai.

Mar. 2021 - Present Cliq Extension Developer.

# **UI/UX Developer (Internship)**

V7lancers, Madurai

Aug. 2021 - Sept 2021

Assisted Technical team in a real time project by designing UI and developing it into a website within the given deadline.

# **Campus Business Manager (Internship)**

Prepbytes, Virtual;

June 2021 - Nov. 2021

Point of contact of Prepbytes at my college.

# **Programming Projects**

#### Minds Eye 2.0

Super Interactive game in Java.

Created a gaming application especially made for ADHD children that would improve their remembrance level and attention span.

#### Care & Cure

Hospital Management System in Java.

A Java Application designed to replace manual paper based system used in hospitals to maintain patient information, Room availability, Patient invoices and so on with a timely retrieval of any information.

#### Salvador

An Interactive Chat Bot - Perfect Health Partner

A Chat Bot connected to healthcare websites that can help users book appointments with ease and keeps them engaged with various stuffs.

More Projects on Github !!!

# **Academic Background**

# Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science and Engineering

Velammal college of engineering and technlogy Madurai, Tamil Nadu Expected to graduate in 2023 CGPA - 9.31 (upto sem 4)

#### Higher Secondary (XII)

C.E.O.A Matric higher secondary school Madurai, Tamil Nadu 2018 - 2019 Percentage - 87.83%

#### Secondary (X)

C.E.O.A Matric higher secondary school Madurai, Tamil Nadu 2016 - 2017 Percentage - 98.4%

#### **Personal Details**

**D.O.B**: 22/04/2002

Father's Name: Murugan S

Languages known: Tamil, English

# Volunteering

#### **NSS Volunteer**

Actively participated in social activities.

#### **Open Source Contributor**

Contributed to open source projects.

#### **Blog Contributor**

Contributed Many blogs on Hashnode

### **Achievements**

### **Honorable Mentions in ZOHO Cliqtrix'22**

CliqTrix is ZOHO's annual app-building contest in which contestants compete by creating real-time apps on Zoho's messaging platforms.

Rewards: Certificate, Cash Prize, ZOHO Internship Offer.

#### Won 1st Prize in Hack Salvation at Synsara'21

A National level Virtual Hackathon conducted by Sri Sai Ram Engineering college, Chennai.

Rewards: Certificate, Cash Prize.

### **Won 1st Prize in Paplectio**

A Paper presentation contest conducted by CSI State level student convention, TamilNadu Rewards: Certificate, Cash Prize.

#### Winner of Java Programming League

A Coding contest organized by CSE dept. at Velammal college of engineering & Technology, Madurai.

Reward: Certificate.

### **Others**

Attended a 2 days workshop on "Internet of Things (lot)" at National Institute of Technology, Trichy (NIT)

Participated in Toycathon-2021, A National level toy Hackathon organized by central government of India, and led my team to grand finale

Participated in Guinness World Record Event - Most users to take an online computer programming lesson in 24 hours.

### **Declaration**

I hereby declare that all the information given above is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.

Station : Madurai Signature : M.S.

Date: 05/03/2022